Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
Who are you? Visiting hours are over.
I am Draht, one of Aura the
Guillotine's executioners.
I am here to kill you.
I see. Done pretending to negotiate?
We're just getting started.
Uh-huh.
Just so you know, I'm strong.
Stronger than me?
Stronger than Aura the Guillotine.
Doesn't seem like it to me.
Why not?
This fight is already over.
Magical wire, huh?
It's an interesting spell.
So you saved yourself from decapitation
by concentrating mana around your neck.
You're level-headed.
A common mage would've lost her head
without even realizing what had happened.
But this wire is among the
strongest of demonkind's spells.
Humanity's magic doesn't
stand a chance against it.
I'll cut through both
your neck and your mana.
You're right. I doubt I can
do anything about this wire.
That's enough to convince you you've won?
Demons these days are hopeless.
They lack actual battle experience.
This mage...
She took my arm!
You bitch—
Wait! Let's talk this—
That's one down.
If I report this attack to the graf and kill
the other two, surely he'll pardon me.
The guard is dead.
Like a fairy tale
It's a sign the story has reached its end
Like a single passage taken from
A journey that was too long
Of the evil that once cast a shadow
Across this land
And the memories of the short journey
With the hero who defeated it
The story ends
And the hero goes to sleep
Leaving this land with
Days of peace and quiet
The passage of time heartlessly
Makes people forget
Even the tracks left behind by his life
Begin to rust
Just the same
Your words and wishes and courage
Are still inside of me
And they live on
We chose the same path
That's all it was supposed to be
Why is it that at some point
I wanted to understand the reason for
The tears that fall down my cheeks
Even now
If I retrace the journey we walked together
Even though you're not there
I know I'll be able to find it
This is delicious.
My master said any town that serves
tasty food is a good, peaceful town.
Wait!
That must be true of this town, too.
Mr. Stark.
You can't have any.
Let's directly petition Graf Granat
to release Ms. Frieren.
I think it's only a matter of time
until harm comes to this town.
We should release Ms. Frieren from the
dungeon and have her defeat the demons.
That's our only option after all, huh?
We wouldn't stand a chance against them.
Especially not that Lügner guy.
He's unbelievably strong.
He was only looking at Frieren.
Even though we were standing there
next to him with the guards,
he was only looking at Frieren.
It's because he thinks he
can kill us at any time.
My hands still haven't stopped shaking.
See? I even spilled my drink
so it looks like I wet myself.
That's just how strong he is.
You should wipe that up. Let's go.
Lügner and his guys are with the graf.
Worst case, a fight will break out.
That wouldn't stop the party
of heroes from going.
You're right.
If I lost my nerve here, I'd never
be able to face my master again.
Let's go.
You can keep the handkerchief.
Huh?
What's the matter?
I'm paralyzed with fear.
I'm no longer detecting Draht's magic.
He must be dead.
What an idiot. He underestimated her.
Underestimated her?
We are the right-hand men of
Lady Aura. Her executioners.
You think we'd die from merely
underestimating someone?
Who is that mage?
Sorry I kept you waiting.
The mage I captured has escaped.
The soldier guarding her cell was beheaded.
That can't be good.
We'll help you look for her.
Linie is skilled at locating magic—
No, that's all right.
By the way, one of your men
seems to be missing.
He's in the privy. He'll be back soon.
Without asking a servant for directions?
Even I can tell she's a skilled mage.
But she allowed my guards
to seize her without a fight.
She understands the seriousness
of killing a guard.
Lord Lügner, I'll ask you one last time.
Where is your man?
Honestly.
That idiot Draht.
He ruined everything.
It's strange, though.
Now that violence has become the only way
to resolve this mess, I'm overjoyed.
Graf Granat, what are words?
How do they differ from swords?
No matter what we use, the weak die.
Just like this sword's former owner.
Lügner!
In the end, we are wild beasts.
Don't worry. I won't kill you.
You're going to help us remove
this town's defensive barrier.
We should be arriving at
the graf's mansion soon.
Ms. Frieren?
You're Ms. Frieren, aren't you?
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me you broke out of the dungeon.
I didn't have a choice.
Some demon named Draht
attacked me while I was in there.
I defeated him,
but when demons die, they turn into
mana particles and disappear.
What do you mean by that?
He'd already killed the dungeon guard.
The only ones down there were a guard
who had been beheaded using
magical wire and me, a mage.
How would you read that situation?
That you're a guard-killer
who should be executed.
Right? This is becoming a pain.
I'm leaving town.
Wait.
If you leave, the remaining
demons will run wild.
Are you really going to abandon this town?
Why don't you two defeat them?
You make it sound so easy.
We don't stand a chance against them.
You're not going to fight them
just because they're strong?
Besides, I don't think you're
weaker than them at all.
Wait!
We'll fight, okay? At least help us!
I'm begging you!
Peek.
Hey, wait!
Please, Frieren!
You don't know when to give up,
do you? Let's steel ourselves.
But... it's impossible...
Don't be childish.
About ten kilometers from town...
I sense a great deal of mana.
We're being observed.
Aura the Guillotine, one of the
Seven Sages of Destruction.
I hate fighting powerful opponents, too.
All the more reason to finish this quickly.
Should we be sneaking
into the mansion like this?
Would you rather tell the gate guards
that we're here to kill the peace envoys?
It's oddly quiet.
I love magic.
Just as Qual, the Elder Sage of Corruption,
spent most of his life
developing a killing spell...
demons dedicate the entirety of our long
lives to researching a single kind of magic.
We develop our research
daily over years and years.
Ten years from now, our
magics will be even greater,
and we will become even stronger.
But magic is a strange thing.
Flamme the Legendary Mage's
defensive barrier has prevented demons
from invading and protected this town.
Sometimes a spell cast by a genius a thousand
years ago outmatches spells of the present.
I despise geniuses.
They lack the beauty of accumulated effort.
The Granat family has been entrusted with
maintaining the barrier for generations.
If you could allow us into this town,
then there must be a way to control it.
Teach it to me.
I'll give you some time.
Consider it carefully.
Making someone wait is an effective
diplomatic strategy for humans as well.
If you won't talk, then all that
awaits you is further torture.
There must be a grimoire
related to the barrier somewhere.
Search the bedroom. I'll search the study.
You're just that adventurer kid
from this afternoon.
I thought my son had come for me.
You look awful.
Those demons did this to you?
I'll release you.
You're trembling.
Is that a problem?
No. It's valiant.
My dead son was trembling
before he headed off to battle, too.
Damn it. I can't cut the rope.
Is it magical?
Don't worry about me.
I'm done for either way.
Evacuating the townsfolk is more important.
They're not gonna listen without you.
The Granat family crest hangs from my neck.
Show this to the guards,
and they'll do whatever you say.
And speaking so casually to me
is a serious crime in this town, brat.
I know. Given the circumstances,
I'll overlook this offense.
Now go.
I see.
Sorry, old man.
I'm gonna break this
expensive-looking chair.
I can't afford to replace it.
Lord Lügner, a rat.
Graf Granat, do you know him?
No. He's one of the adventurers
from this afternoon.
He must've come to petition me directly
without realizing the mage
he was with escaped.
What a stupid kid.
I see.
Again.
You can leave, boy.
I'll let you live.
He's doing it again.
He's not even looking at me.
What's the matter? Move.
If you get in my way, I'll kill you.
Go ahead and try!
He's fast.
But you're only human.
You protected your vitals.
Your reflexes aren't bad.
That said, the young are rash,
whether they're humans or demons—
thoughtless and reckless.
But you challenged me alone.
I commend your valor.
Alone?
I see. You can't detect her after all.
What?
Fern, I created the opening you asked for.
Lord Lügner, I'm sensing a mage!
Impossible.
A mere human mage evaded Linie's detection?
And this spell...
Lord Lügner, let me handle this.
Don't.
Girl, what is that spell?
Ordinary offensive magic.
I believe it's known as Zoltraak
in your magic system.
This is Zoltraak?
Don't be absurd.
Demonkind overcame Zoltraak
half a century ago.
Who taught you this spell?
You're trying to buy time, aren't you?
I should finish you now.
I won't allow it.
Fern!
The graf is gravely injured.
We don't have time to fight.
Let's retreat!
Very well.
We'll go after them once
I've stopped my bleeding.
You kill the warrior.
My blood is on those two.
We won't lose them.
You needn't fight them yourself, Lord Lügner.
I can handle the mage as well.
If you'd been struck by that spell,
it would've killed you.
That spell has been modified
to specialize in killing demons.
It can hardly be called Zoltraak anymore.
It's a demon-killing spell.
The way that girl moved
reminds me of another mage.
And I've been struck by
that same magic once before.
I see.
I remember now.
It was Frieren.
The mage who contributed significantly
to humanity's analysis of Zoltraak
and slew more demons
than anyone else in history.
Frieren the Slayer.
One of the geniuses I despise.
And you alright
Can you hear me
Trailing along deserted train tracks
Crying excessively
Wanting you to smile
I hold on to memories I'd like to keep fresh
There's something I'd like to tell you
With words more precious than a goodbye
Unremarkable yet special
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
So, if I were to be born again
I would surely choose this place once more
So, if we were to meet again
I'd never let you go, I'd choose the present
Even if no promises were made
Even if I'm lost in days of loneliness
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
Lord Lügner will be upset with me again.
Seriously? This is crazy.
You'll have to rest for a while.
You demons are monsters after all.
Any demon can do it.
Because I have an overwhelming advantage.
I can kill you without mercy.
It was Aura, one of the
Seven Sages of Destruction.